## Steven Mu

2203 Maywind Way, Hacienda Heights, CA 91745 · (626) 566-1307 · stevenwmu@gmail.com

Success-driven sales, business development, and partnerships leader with more than 7 years Fintech Payments and 4 years of financial consulting experience delivering revenue and market gains for international corporations. Strong record of strategy development, outperforming revenue goals, driving new business, and building strong partner/customer relationships at all levels. Excellent communication and customer focused problem-solving skills. Fluent in English and Mandarin

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Citcon, Inc, San Jose, CA

## Executive Director of Partnerships

July 2021 - November 2022

Citcon's payment platform provides seamless commerce to merchants worldwide by enabling global alternative payment methods.

- Established new partnerships with top financial institutions (banks, processors, gateways), ISVs, ISOs, and wallet supply partners critical to Citcon's growth
- Defined a comprehensive omnichannel and ecommerce partnerships strategy. Providing business leadership, creative direction and driving goals
- Negotiated and managed all elements of partnership contracts which included evaluating new products/services, pricing, business terms, and service level agreements
- Managed partner integration/implementation projects and cultivated strong relationships with key decision makers
- Drove partnerships engagement to generate merchant leads and bring incremental revenue to the company. Exceeded 2021 KPI for merchant referrals from partner.
- Collaborated with cross-functional stakeholders to represent business and technical trade-offs

**ID TECH, Cypress, CA** 

Director of Business Development Director of Sales, North America June 2020 – June 2021 February 2016 – May 2020

ID TECH is a leading payment hardware and solutions provider based in North America, Europe and Asia.

- As Director of Business Development, I led the North American distribution strategy by working with distributors, resellers, ISO, and ISVs to certify and market our payments solutions.
- Supplemented Asia sales team by identifying key verticals and strategy, opening the door for sales team withing new prospects and helping team close deals
- Drove product management/marketing decisions sand provide input on high-level company strategic direction
- As Director of Sales, I was responsible for the retention and growth of the North America region (ID TECH's largest region) through B2B direct sales and indirect sales to all levels of the payments environment
- Managed a team of 4 sales managers and 2 inside sales which exceeded 2019 revenue goal

Thecus Technology Corp, Taipei, Taiwan

Territory Sales Manager

October 2011 – December 2013

Thecus Technology Corporation is a Taiwanese multinational corporation that designs and markets computer storage solutions.

- Responsible for developing and executing Sales/Marketing strategies to surpass objectives and sales goals for Australia, UK, Germany and South American territories

- Implemented incentive programs with partners resulting in 15% revenue increase in both 2012 and 2013
- Brokered distribution contracts, pricing, and signed multiple new clients
- Hosted new product media press conference and conducted client training at global consumer electronic trade shows
- Oversaw territory budgets and corporate direction relating to future revenue goals

# **Profit Recovery Partners, LLC, Irvine, California** *Consultant, Solutions Management*

August 2007 – June 2009

Profit Recovery Partners is a professional services firm developing financial solutions for companies throughout North America.

- Managed annual customer expenses of 12 million USD and reduced customer operational expenses resulting in annual savings over 2.8 million USD
- Analyzed client contracts and purchasing data to negotiate with vendors and implemented improved solutions
- Created customized cost reduction plans on a case-by-case basis focused on client retention.
- Administrated new vendor implementation for various client business processes
- Led frequent meetings with Fortune 1000 CEOs, CFOs, and Controllers and conducted various internal professional development presentations.

### **EDUCATION**

National Taiwan Normal University, Taipei, Taiwan

Mandarin Training Center

University of California, Riverside, Riverside, California

February 2010 – Sept 2011

Bachelor of Arts in Economics/Administrative Studies

June 2007